
[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "It’s important that facilitators are aware of _____ that can occur online.",
    "answer": "Assumptions and misinterpretations",
    "correct": "Assumptions and misinterpretations",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "As a facilitator, it is important to establish a ____ for conversations.",
    "answer": "Code of conduct",
    "correct": "Code of conduct",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "_____ is a key facilitating skill that consists of keeping discussions moving.",
    "answer": "Weaving",
    "correct": "Weaving",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Facilitators should use their______ – this is how they represent themselves online and relate to others.",
    "answer": "Social presence",
    "correct": "Social presence",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "It is easy for misunderstandings to occur in online settings where the _____ cues are missing.",
    "answer": "Physical and verbal",
    "correct": "Physical and verbal",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "It’s important that facilitators are aware of _____ that can occur online.",
    "answer": "Assumptions and misinterpretations",
    "correct": "6",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "As a facilitator, it is important to establish a ____ for conversations.",
    "answer": "Code of conduct",
    "correct": "7",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "_____ is a key facilitating skill that consists of keeping discussions moving.",
    "answer": "Weaving",
    "correct": "8",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Facilitators should use their______ – this is how they represent themselves online and relate to others.",
    "answer": "Social presence",
    "correct": "9",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "It is easy for misunderstandings to occur in online settings where the _____ cues are missing.",
    "answer": "Physical and verbal",
    "correct": "10",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "Facilitators should use their______ – this is how they represent themselves online and relate to others.",
    "answer": "Social presence",
    "correct": "11",
    "feedBackText": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "type": "choice",
    "question": "It is easy for misunderstandings to occur in online settings where the _____ cues are missing.",
    "answer": "Physical and verbal",
    "correct": "12",
    "feedBackText": ""
  }
]






